A Guide to the Papers of the Albermarle Aircraft Warning Service
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Albermarle Aircraft Warning Service
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
2040
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- Correspondence 1941 April 25- 1943 Mar. 31, n.d., 8 folders (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1943 Apr. 1-1944 May 31, 3 folders (Box 2)
- Applications and records re: gas rationing 1942 May 11- 1943 Jul. 23 (Box 2)
- Bulletins to chief observers and observation post headquarters 1941 Dec. 10- 1944 May 29, n.d. (Box 2)
- Bulletins for all observers 1942 Jan 2.- 1943 Jun 12., n.d. (Box 2)
- Lists of observers and newsletters 1942 Mar.-1943 Jul. 15, n.d.
- Newsclippings 1941 Jun 6.-1943 Oct. 5, n.d. (Box 2)
- Reports from posts 1942 Jan. 7- 1943 Nov. 11 (Box 3)
- Schedules for posts 1942 Dec. 6- Mar. 22 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous, including public relations material 1939 May 15-1944 May 31, n.d., 2 folders (Box 3)
- Armbands and Buttons ca. 1944 (Box 3)